(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I'm trying to raise the temperature
in here...
(Sheldon:)...before my nipples
tear through my shirt.
(Howard:)Why don't you
just turn up the thermostat?
Aha. Good question.
It turns out that the thermostat
for my new office isn't in my new office.
(Sheldon:)No, it's next door
in Professor Davenport's office...
(Sheldon:)...who is currently enjoying the hot
flashes associated with menopause.
(Leonard:)Why is there a hole here?
Why is there a hole in my new office?
l've narrowed it down
to two possibilities.
There was something in the wall
that someone outside the wall wanted.
Or the more disturbing...
...there was something in the wall
that wanted out.
At least you got a window that opens.
That's nice.